I've been
spending most of my time at Nvidia.
We've raised around $51 million. No
pressure.
We'll put all Kelly's stuff in the
design. So, Kelly, our intern, says
[music] she's going to grab us coffee.
Number one intern 2.0. Okay.
Today, I'll be working as an intern at
an AI company called Vizcom. Let's head
[music] in.
Hi.
>> [laughter]
>> How's your day going? Pretty good. Still
waking up.
Where did you get the Yes, here. I'll
let Kaylin open it. Oh, we we got him a
first birthday like this like Pop Mart.
Oh.
Oh, there he is. Kaylin.
Kaylin, this is Kelly. She's actually
from Michigan as well. He's also from
Michigan. Yes.
>> from Michigan, too?
>> Yeah. Yes. We're both from the same
place, Rochester.
>> Really? Yeah. Yeah. Lovely to meet a
fellow Michigander. Yes.
So, we're at Vizcom now. So, this is our
headquarters in San Francisco. We build
a lot of software for designers. The
computer that you're watching this
through started out as a drawing
somewhere, and we help people turn those
drawings into things that they can
actually hold. So, yeah, I studied
industrial design, and essentially spent
most of my time at Nvidia. I used to be
a car designer, as well, at Honda. And
then, yeah, started Vizcom about like 4
years ago after that. So, up till today,
we've raised around $51 million. We
recently just closed our Series B, which
is super exciting. It's a huge milestone
for the company. Congratulations. That's
incredible. Thank you. Thank you. Thank
you. How did you learn Korean? I used to
live in Korea studying industrial
design. As time just went on, making
friends and like KTalk and watching
shows, I just started to learn Korean.
He's super fluent. Cuz he's really good.
>> [laughter]
>> I checked out your website. I played
around on it. I even drew my own thing.
>> Really? Yeah, I I did. And it was really
impressive. So, I'm excited to explore
it more today.
>> Totally. Cool. So, we are currently
upstairs. So, this is where the sales
team sits, some people from marketing.
We actually don't have like assigned
seating just yet. We're still kind of
figuring that out. And then, we have
kind of this like kitchen area. Today is
Wednesday, so like team lunch
Wednesdays. And then, yeah, we'll kind
of like eat up here. Wow! This is
awesome.
>> It's just funny to see the agents agents
on the billboards again.
You know in Michigan it's like oh,
lawyers are you in a crash? Like or the
ads are just so different like San
Francisco has
This is kind of where a lot of the
engineering and design team works. So,
that's Jared. Hi Jared. Jared's here.
See, he has this the cactus thing and
>> What is it? A community member from the
this company designed this cactus and
we're making it real by prototyping it
downstairs with That is so cool.
So, yeah, this is the maker space and
this is where we do a lot of 3D
printing. [music]
These are some other 3D parts of what
Jared's working on upstairs. So, this is
kind of actually going to be a coat rack
that you put these pieces on like this.
That is cool.
This is where we kind of like film
random videos [music] sometimes. Let's
see this section. Oh!
>> [laughter]
>> Wow! This is amazing.
Sophia who you'll meet later, she
[music] did all this. She she's worked
at Webflow doing like production stuff
and content creation. She just like
assembled this. Oh my gosh! We need a
Sophia.
It's like I was like they're like we
need a Soph. I'm Cali. Lovely to meet
you. Nice meeting you, too. My whole
background is in film production before
tech. And then I worked at a company
called Webflow before that. We had a
bunch of satellite studios that I helped
to build.
>> Webflow as the the web builder you know?
I used to use that. Yeah, if you go on
Webflow University, I'm in a bunch of
their videos. Oh! All right, I'm in.
Okay, cool. Our job here now is to
really understand how to convert this
media content into like a LinkedIn kind
of format. So,
>> I think what I would do is maybe do the
frame it as a question. I know we've
done that post that type of post before
where it's more thought leadership-y.
So, that is what I would probably do.
>> Yes. with this example. Okay, that's a
really good idea. How do we now from a
content formatting perspective you think
like
>> to include in terms of imagery? Yeah, do
you think we should turn some of these
like videos into GIFs potentially? We
could.
Yeah, awesome. So
Who was supposed to do this right now?
Here you go.
Okay, okay, okay.
Oh, no.
Look at this little wall.
All right, we'll try this again. All
right, so yeah, let that go through.
Awesome.
Great. Who's usually watching like the
LinkedIn [music] post? How what's your
target audience? With Instagram, that's
really where our like designer like
collective I would say [music] is.
LinkedIn is more so I think targeting
folks who may not know what Viscom is.
So, I think like [music] it's more so
like prospect customers on LinkedIn. The
students who are looking to build their
design portfolios, who are studying
industrial design, they come to [music]
Viscom to see like examples. We have a
webinar tomorrow and there's a lot of
students signed up for it. Is it mostly
in US like American viewers?
>> As far as the students go, we've
definitely seen like a global region. I
even hosted in Korea like 3 weeks ago in
Namyang all the way where my mom is and
like cuz their design studio there uses
Viscom. Yeah,
we're getting there. We're good. Yeah,
that's great. That's great. Beautiful.
Amazing.
I will give you your assignment now. So,
there's going to be multiple tasks. The
first task here is to help us grab some
coffee. As the intern in Viscom, we need
our coffee for energy. And then when you
get back, we're going to need you to
design a flyer of sorts for this design
challenge we have coming up where it
involves people that are going to use
cork materials to design different
objects. Okay. And we'd love to get your
take on that. Then we'll have some of
the other team members check out what
you make as well. So, yeah, no pressure.
Yeah. No pressure. This is going to go
into production. We'll We'll put Oh,
Kelly some design. Oh, no.
>> [laughter]
>> Okay, I can do it. I can do it. I got
this. Let me get some orders. The banana
cappuccino.
>> Banana cappuccino?
>> That sounds great. Do you have a
preference on the milk? Do you like the
goat's milk or Just regular milk is
totally fine. Okay.
>> So, Kelly, our intern today, she's going
to grab us coffee from Golden Goat.
[laughter]
Ice latte? Any milk preference? Ice
latte? Big strawberry matcha latte. Ooh,
fancy.
Okay, awesome. Number one intern, 2026.
I'm already sweating. I can't mess this
up. [laughter]
Golden Goat is like super known for like
having really cool specialty coffees.
Jordan really likes the banana bread
cappuccino.
>> That's what he did. He did the banana
Live in Korea? We do, yeah.
Yeah, we came for a Coachella and then
spent like a little less than 2 weeks
here in SF. Did you see Justin Bieber?
Yeah.
Okay, it's right here, actually. Oh,
okay. Hi.
Hi, I have a really big order. Is that
okay? It's all to go. Sure.
Are all these under the same name?
>> Yeah, please. Cali. An ice latte with
whole milk, ice latte with oat milk, two
iced strawberry matchas.
Oh, you don't have any?
Just regular matcha, then?
Okay. Light sweet should be good, yeah.
Also, we're going to be carrying these.
Do you have any like
Okay. Okay.
Thank you so much. Goodbye.
Oh, our lunch is here. Lunchtime.
Is this the cappuccino?
Orange cappuccino? No, I think the
orange cappuccino is um Kyle's. Kyle's.
Did we get a regular cappuccino?
No worries. I'm
panicking.
>> [laughter]
>> Did I fail my mission? Cappuccino.
Sweet. Do you guys live in Korea or do
you guys live here now? Korea.
Mhm. So it's Busan it was like a little
more chill.
>> It is. It is. Especially we lived like
right in Gangnam before moving to Busan.
And it's just like the vibes are so
different cuz it's all offices and it's
just like the hustle bustle. But then
Busan we live on the beach and it's a
lot of like tourists and travelers. How
many Do you guys feel the 10 days?
Living in Seoul is like insane. Yes.
Wow. We eat like close to four five
times I think. And the tips is like out
of here.
Even like you know I'm born and raised
American but every time I come back I'm
like
>> [laughter]
>> And then I get confused too cuz I'm like
at like a kiosk or something and always
pops up you know like I don't want to
pay. I don't want to answer that.
Yeah.
We kicking it like twice since we've
been here.
I like it. It's a really smart but I
just get like nervous anxious a little
bit still. Like I still got to get used
to it. What do you do like when you need
to like go to the bathroom or something?
Needs a pause button or something.
>> [laughter]
>> Happy birthday [singing]
to you.
Happy birthday
Cake. Cake. Thank you.
So yummy. They've got some fresh [music]
fruits in there. So good.
So can you just introduce yourself and
talk about what you do at Viscom? Yeah
so my name is Amy. I'm a product design
engineer here at Viscom. I will like
think of new features design them like
write code to implement them into the
Viscom tool and then
get some feedback from our customers to
iterate on that and make sure it's
something that they'll use at their
design jobs. Awesome. Thank you so much.
Hi. I'm Onur Kırkpınar. I'm a product
manager here at Viscom. Been working
here for about a year and a half. My
background is as industrial designer,
automotive designer, so the natural fit
working at Viscom.
>> What kind of like a regular day at
Viscom look like for you? Usually
throughout the day I'm testing new
models, maybe spinning up some POCs.
Sometimes we'll have calls with users to
be able to beta test new features,
understand what their pain points are.
>> Thank you so much. I appreciate it.
>> So, my name is Brandon. I'm a product
engineer here at Viscom. I'm mainly
working on like the dashboard and
helping out admins, but the latest thing
that I've been working on [music] is
a third-party integration with Fusion.
It's like a 3D modeling tool. A lot of
our customers like working in like
external applications, whether it's like
3D modeling or like Photoshop. We can
hook into these other tools that they
like using and making like the workflow
a lot more seamless. So, I'm Al
Handalzer. I'm the head of sales at
Viscom. Yeah, usually we're going on
site, spending a day or two with their
leadership team and their designers to
train them on how to use the product.
Like we've been to Korea several times
to go see like Hyundai, Kia, some of our
customers there. What did you think of
Korea? I love it.
>> [laughter]
>> I love it. Yeah, yeah. Did you get the
experience in Korea of going out, having
drinks and like
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah, the team at Hyundai took
us out for soju and Korean barbecue and
like we put soju on top of the cast, you
know? Yeah, yeah, we did the whole
thing, which was a lot of fun. Uh great
question. So, yeah, I think a lot of it
has been actually inbound interest cuz
the the product is our secret weapon.
The product is just so good that people
are really drawn to it. Like every
morning we wake up with a few new ones.
Awesome. Thank you so much. Really
appreciate it. So, I am Audrey. I am the
executive assistant to both co-founders
here at Viscom, Jordan and Kaylin. I do,
you know, like calendar management,
inbox management, just kind of like
managing their schedules and like
coordinating where they need to be at
what time and I'm just kind of helping
everyone on the team make sure we're all
moving efficiently. I always joke with
Jordan like I wish I could like clone
you or like put a microchip in your
brain so I knew what you were thinking
at all times. Can you maybe give a tip
for time management, organization,
communication, anything that like you
>> Yeah, I really like the Eisenhower
matrix. I'm not sure if you've heard of
it, but it's a kind of like a diagram or
chart where you can like prioritize
different things, especially working
with two different founders. One's like
the technical, the CTO, one's the CEO.
Juggling priorities and like what to
actually get to first is sometimes
challenging. So, that's been really
helpful for me. Yeah. Thank you so much.
Yeah, move on.
Hello, my name is Kim. I'm a growth
marketer at Vizcom. So, some of the work
I do here is hosting like challenges,
on-site events, activations at Design
Week, as well as looking at how we can
grow our broader self-serve user base,
so those that are signing up for our
website. Hi, I'm Mara. I'm the senior
brand and web designer here at Vizcom. I
work pretty closely with Kim to help
create some of the promotional assets,
update the website, and really drive
buzz for the challenge. All right, so
what are we doing today, exactly? Once
Kim kind of comes up with the timeline
and who we're working with, what we'll
start with is by creating some assets
that we can use for a launch. So, just
some sample objects of what the
challenge is.
Draw a line like that, right? Mhm.
No?
Uh you draw the line and then you
connect when you let go. Okay. Put the
plants
into the planter. Yeah, it helps if you
target the [music] object, so it's like
Perfect.
It's like onboarding interns.
>> Yes.
Thank you so much.
Okay, so I will show you Okay, moment of
truth here. So, this is what the team
and I worked on. Oh.
>> Yeah, we actually did this on Vizcom.
Oh, cool. So, you got in there. Can I
see this real quick? Oh, wow. That is
awesome. So, this is all cork down here.
Yep. Very cool. I wish there was like
more showcase of the cork itself. It's
hard to tell maybe from this image that
cork is the special thing about this. Or
also understanding like why cork. But
all in all, I mean like the actual
execution is super cool. It's your your
your first intern project of sorts. So,
great job. Awesome stuff. Thank you. A
plus.
Yes.
>> [laughter]
>> I had a great time like talking to
everyone here and [music] getting to
spend the day here. So, really thank you
so much.
>> Yeah. Is there anything you want to say
[music] lastly? Maybe about this
conference, to the viewers, or Thanks
for watching, guys. Yeah, don't forget
to like, comment, and subscribe. Love
you, boy.
>> [laughter]
>> Bye.
Thank you. Thank you. Bye. Nice Nice
meeting you. Thank you for coming. Yeah,
thank you. Nice meeting you.